



# Fatmanisa Mumpuni Delta Maharani

**Date of birth:** 17/03/2001 | **Nationality:** Indonesian | **Gender:** Female |

Phone number: (+62) 85854413732 (Mobile) | Email address:

<u>fatmanisamaharani@gmail.com</u> | **LinkedIn:** 

https://www.linkedin.com/in/fatmanisa-mumpuni-a07b42268

Address: Jl Puncak Jaya II No 15C, 64211, Kediri, Indonesia (Home)

#### **ABOUT ME**

A fresh graduate in Information System, who always expand experience and knowledge. An enthuastic & driven learner, who looking to enhance my knowledge in analytical data business intelligence sector. My previous project experience have provided me how to execute data with a various process such as scrapping, cleansing, validation etc. Has work experience in the field of financial administration staff at Wirasaba Vocational High School for more than two years. On the other hand, I also work well with team members as well as alone. Reflecting on my previous responsibility I was assigned by the superior to handle the secretary and treasurer role for some projects.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

01/08/2019 - 24/04/2023 Karawang, Indonesia

#### FINANCE ADMINISTRATION STAFF SMK WIRASABA

- Manage and filling school administration documents both printed and non-printed by archiving each category
- Ensuring any business trip works properly by creating a business trip letter for the correct party in line with budget planning.
- Preparing financial statements once a (week/month) to ease the director's review current budget already aligns or not with the plan.
- Cooperate with external parties for operational purposes such as reporting BOS for any school operational funds, maintaining good relationships between other schools, and joining the training if any technology update.

Business or Sector Education | Email <a href="mailto:smk.wirasaba@yahoo.com">smk.wirasaba@yahoo.com</a> | Website <a href="http://www.smkwirasaba.com">http://www.smkwirasaba.com</a>

01/09/2023 - CURRENT Kediri, Indonesia

# **ADMINISTRATION SECRETARY REGIONAL PEOPLE'S REPRESENTATIVE ASSEMBLY**

- Manage administration of legisltavie candidates
- Manage outgoing and incoming mail
- Manage the campaign schedule for legisltaive candidates
- Form a field coordination team
- Check the permanent electoral list for ballot papers

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/09/2019 - 11/03/2023 Karawang, Indonesia

# BACHELOR DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE Buana Perjuangan University

- · Looking for the best comparison of two algorithms with many objects from ewallet
- Analyze the problems that exist in each ewallet through customer data assessment surveys
- Make a raw data design that has been taken to become a mature data result of a comparison of the two algorithms

Address Jl. HS.Ronggo Waluyo, Puseurjaya, Telukjambe Timur, Karawang, Jawa Barat, 41361, Karawang, Indonesia

Field of study Information and Communication Technologies | Final grade Cumlaude |

**Thesis** Perbandingan Metode Klasifikasi Sentimen Analisis Penggunaan E-Wallet Mengunakan Algoritma Naive Bayes dan KNearest Neighbor

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): INDONESIA

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	A2	B1	A2	A2	B1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

### DIGITAL SKILLS

#### Softskill

Good work ethics and personal behavior | hope, efficacy, resilience, and optimism | Organizational and planning skills | Team-work oriented | Good listener and communicator

#### Hardskill

Microsoft Office package: Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access | Programming: PHP, Framework Codelgniter, Boostrap, Javascript | Google (Google Drive, Google Docs, Google Slides, Google Sheets, Google Meets, Google Trends)) | Social Media / Social Network

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

# **SOCIAL AND POLITICAL ACTIVITIES**

27/10/2020 - 11/07/2021 Buana Perjuangan University, Karawang

Secretary of the Information System Student Association Organization

- Responsible for the implementation of the meeting
- Responsible for the provision of facilities and other secretarial infrastructure
- Together with the chairman signed the exit papers
- Making reports on organizational activities

# **CERTIFICATE AND TRAINING**

06/11/2021 - 06/11/2021

Softskill Series 1 oleh Komunitas IT Karawang-Bekasi (Komitkabe)

Dengan tema: "Etika & Budaya Kerja"

Link https://drive.google.com/file/d/1GZrQdMzWv-ltel1DNDSyF\_P9P1\_dp-Wz/view?usp=drive\_link

20/11/2021 - 21/11/2021

Softskill Series 2 oleh Fakultas Psikologi Universitas Buana Perjuangan

Dengan tema: "Hope, Efficacy, Resilience, and Optimism"

Link https://drive.google.com/file/d/1EoBPzSOvRbl8yMgQtyrJm-uQX3S51A1M/view?usp=drive\_link

27/11/2021 - 28/11/2021

Softskill Series 3 oleh Sang Surya

Dengan tema: "Personal CHAMPION (Clarity, Honesty, Action, Mastery, Priority, Integrity, Opportunity, Needed)"

Link https://drive.google.com/file/d/1GnYYSHCuNraVcAy-hqM-\_xmOldQ3mpaD/view?usp=drive\_link

22/06/2021 - 22/06/2021

Literasi Digital Nasional oleh Kementrian Komunikasi dan Informatika Republik Indonesia

Dengan tema: "Untuk Indonesia Makin Cakap Digital"

Link https://drive.google.com/file/d/1EoES3aWw61evGZ 7n-b-UAma5bNZbR-x/view?usp=drive\_link

04/06/2022 - 04/06/2022

Webinar Pekan Raya Sistem Informasi oleh Himpunan Mahasiswa Sistem Informasi UBPK

Dengan tema: "A Day In My Life As A Software Engineer"

Link https://drive.google.com/file/d/1jd9KYCUmErTHWtlY9NhD8teEY2t\_uzFF/view?usp=drive\_link

21/09/2020 - 21/09/2020

Workshop WEB DEVELOPMENT oleh Himpunan Mahasiswa Sistem Informasi UBPK

oleh R Sandhika Galih Amalga, M.T.

Link https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ELGb8IYD1IdQ\_mlZJK6kdQxi4bspUeY\_/view?usp=drive\_link

01/02/2020 - 01/02/2020

Seminar Nasional Bigdata 2020 oleh Himpunan Mahasiswa Sistem Informasi UBPK

Dengan tema: "Optimalisasi Pemanfaatan Teknologi Informasi dan Bigdata Di Era Revolusi 4.0" oleh Ir. Onno Purbo, M. Eng., Ph.D & Dr. Andry Alamsyah, S.Si., M.Sc

 $\textbf{Link} \ \underline{\text{https://drive.google.com/file/d/1mYe0wm6hGlA96SKjWzBrij0c-sOlz3RO/view?usp=drive\_link} \\$